<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Welcome to my website on Welcome to my homepage</title>
    <link>http://robinjacobroy.github.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Welcome to my website on Welcome to my homepage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 13:44:52 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://robinjacobroy.github.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Research Projects</title>
      <link>http://robinjacobroy.github.com/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 10:12:03 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://robinjacobroy.github.com/projects/</guid>
      <description>Here are the various Computer vision projects I worked on:
 Protein Particle extraction from cryo-EM micrographs using Sematic Segmentation. Odonata Detetion Using YOLO algorithm Tree canopy delination using U-net Drosophila melogaster activity recognition using CNN Mathematical symbol recognition Image Enhancement using Pix2Pix GAN Identification of freshwater fishes from underwater camera feeds.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications and Presentations</title>
      <link>http://robinjacobroy.github.com/presnpub/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 17:10:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://robinjacobroy.github.com/presnpub/</guid>
      <description>Blesson George, Anshul Assaiya, Robin Jacob Roy, Ajit Kembhavi, Radha Chauhan, Geetha Paul, Janesh Kumar, Ninan Sajeeth Philip. “CASSPER is a semantic segmentation‐based particle picking algorithm for single‐particle cryo‐electron microscopy”. Communications Biology ‐ Nature. February 2021.  Conference Presentations:   “Image Enhancement using Deep Learning GAN” at the National Seminar, NSAMAP‐2023, organized by St. Thomas College Kozhencherry in January 2023.
  “Automated Feature Extraction and Classification of Odonates” at the National Seminar, SIAP‐2019, organized by Govt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://robinjacobroy.github.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 10:15:15 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://robinjacobroy.github.com/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m Robin Jacob Roy. I&amp;rsquo;m working as a Computer Vision researcher at airis4D, Thelliyoor and has a profound knowledge on various Computer Vision techniques in Python.
Checkout my résumé
Rach me out at:
 Github LinkedIn Twitter  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>